pensamientos.com 2019-04-28

# PRIVACY – Pensamientos

Privacy Policy – Pensamientos.com

Pensamientos.com is serious about protecting your online privacy. This  
Privacy Statement explains our views and practices concerning privacy,  
and how they may pertain to you as a user of our website.

“You” or “Your” means you as a participant in or as a user of the  
Pensamientos.com website. “We” or “Our” or “Us” means  
Pensamientos.com. “Our site” means Pensamientos.com.

SECTION 1 – WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?

When you purchase something from our site, as part of the buying and  
selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such  
as your name, address and email address. This enables us to both  
fulfill and support the products you purchase.

When you browse our site, we also automatically receive your  
computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with  
information that helps us learn about your browser and operating  
system so we can better improve the experience for all our users.

Email marketing: With your permission, we may send you emails about  
new products, free and premium content (i.e. blog posts, YouTube  
videos, reports/whitepapers, etc.), and special events.

SECTION 2 – CONSENT

When you provide us with personal information to complete a  
transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a  
delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our  
collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason (i.e.  
newsletter subscription and marketing messages), we will ask you  
directly for your expressed consent and provide you with an  
opportunity to withdraw your consent.

You may withdraw your consent at any time by clicking on an  
“unsubscribe” link which is offered at the bottom of every email we  
send.

You may also withdraw your consent anytime, by contacting us at  
support@pensamientos.com or mailing us at: Pensamientos.com , C/O  
Nokan Investments S.A., Ofibodegas Capri Local #3, San José, Costa  
Rica.

SECTION 3 – DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to  
do so or if you violate our Terms of Service. Also, if our site is  
acquired or merged with another company, your information may be  
transferred to the new owners so that they may continue to sell and  
support our products and services.

IMPORTANT: We do not sell, rent or otherwise disclose your personal  
information to any third parties, including but not limited to  
advertisers, strategic partners or vendors. Again, we take your  
privacy very seriously.

SECTION 4 – DATA STORAGE

We do not collect any personal data.

SECTION 5 – THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect,  
use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow  
them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment  
gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own  
privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to  
provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies  
so you can understand the manner in which your personal information  
will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or  
have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either  
you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves  
the services of a third-party service provider, then your information  
may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that  
service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is  
processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your  
personal information used in completing that transaction may be  
subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the  
Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party  
website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy  
Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

Links: When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away  
from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of  
other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

SECTION 6 – SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions  
and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not  
inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or  
destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information  
is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored  
with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the  
Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS  
requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry  
standards.

SECTION 7 – COOKIES

Pensamientos.com utilizes cookies to create a more customized  
experience for our users and customers. For example, we use a login  
cookie so members do not have to re-enter their username and password  
each time they return to our site We also use tracking pixels (i.e.  
Google Analytics) to aid in measuring and tracking where our website  
traffic is coming from and to track the performance of our site.  
Finally, we use remarking pixels from Facebook and Google to aid in  
customized, targeted followup advertising.

SECTION 8 – AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of  
majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the  
age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have  
given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use  
this site.

SECTION 9 – CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so  
please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take  
effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make  
material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has  
been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect,  
how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or  
disclose it.

QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal  
information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want  
more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at  
support@pensamientos.com or by mail at Pensamientos.com

[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]

[Nokan Investments S.A., Ofibodegas Capri Local #3, San José, Costa Rica]
